dealereprocess.com 2015-06-11

# Privacy Policy - Dealer E Process

## Information regarding Dealer e-Process’ privacy practices:

* * *

This document describes Dealer e-Process’ policy regarding standard information collected in normal web site usage as well as information you provide when you visit our web site. The amount and type of information received depends on how you use our site.

### Normal Web Site Usage:

During normal web site usage, we do not collect or store personally identifiable information such as name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number, or social security number. You can visit Dealer e-Process’ web site to read product, company, and other information. The only information we collect and store during normal web site usage is the name of your Internet service provider, the web site you last visited, the pages you request, and the date and time of those requests. We collect this information to generate statistics and measure site activity to improve the usefulness of customer visits. This information is shared only within Dealer e-Process.

### Collection of Personal Information:

At times, particularly when you use one of our online services (i.e., new-car buying, used-car buying, Dealer e-Process’ online credit application, etc.), Dealer e-Process may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to fill out any one of these forms. If you choose to use one of these online services, however, Dealer e-Process may require that you provide information, which may include your name, mailing address, e-mail address, social security number or other personally identifying information. When you submit personal information to Dealer e-Process, you understand and agree that Dealer e-Process may access, store, and utilize your customer profile information. We may share information about your personal information with reputable credit reporting agencies as authorized under federal and state laws, but only as lawfully permitted or required. We collect this information for a variety of reasons, including but not limited to informing you of special offers, and other products and services from Dealer e-Process.

While we have not done so at this time, in the future we may contract with other reputable companies in our efforts to offer you additional attractive products and services. If you do not want the information you provide to Dealer e-Process to be shared with other companies, please indicate this preference when you provide the information to Dealer e-Process in the comments section. Of course, we will honor your request.

Dealer e-Process’ privacy practices are designed to provide a high level of protection for your personal information and our computer systems.

### Interest-Based/Online Behavioral Advertising:

Interest-Based/Online Behavioral Advertising. On some pages of our site we may allow third-party advertising partners to set web tracking tools (e.g., cookies and web beacons) to collect anonymous, non-personally identifiable information regarding your activities on those pages (e.g., your IP address, page(s) visited, time of day). We may also share such information we have collected with third-party advertising partners. These advertising partners may use this information (and similar information collected from other websites) for purposes of delivering future targeted advertisements to you when you visit other sites within their networks. This practice is commonly referred to as “interest-based advertising” or “online behavioral advertising.”

A “cookie” is a small text file or text identifier placed on your computer to assist us in providing customized services. We use cookies to provide you with a convenience feature to save you time and provide a more personalized experience on our site. For example, you may log on once during a visit and will be able to access multiple servers without having to log on again and again. We also use the information for internal research on our user’s demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand our visitor’s preferences. We may use cookies provided by Google . You have the ability to accept or decline cookies.

You may elect to refuse cookies. Please refer to your browser Help instructions to learn more about cookies and how to manage their use

* * *

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy. A revised Privacy Policy will only apply to data collected subsequent to its effective date. Any revisions will be posted at least 10 days prior to its effective date.
